Sculptors Guild
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Exhibition Files, circa 1938-1979, Series 4:; (Boxes 4, 9, OV 10; 0.5 linear feet)
  Exhibition announcements and catalogs are followed by files arranged alphabetically by name of exhibition and chronologically thereafter.
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, circa 1938-1958, 1966-1970, (5 folders) (Box 4)
  - Bryant Park Exhibition, 1966-1969, (2 folders; see also Box 9, OV 10; Reel 5909: 898-1034) (Box 4)
  - Contemporary Arts Building, World's Fair, New York, 1939-1940, (2 folders; see also Box 9; Reel 5909: 251-313) (Box 4)
  - Lever House Exhibition, 1959-1979, (12 folders; Reel 5909: 485-897) (Box 4)
  - New Members Exhibition, 1969, (Reel 5909: frames 1035-1037) (Box 4)
  - Outdoor Exhibition, 1939, (Reel 5909: frames 469-480) (Box 4)
  - Outdoor Exhibition, 1948, (see also OV 10; Reel 5909: frames 481-484) (Box 4)
  - Traveling Exhibition, 1939-1941, (Reel 5909: frames 314-409) (Box 4)
  - Traveling Exhibition, 1953-1954, (Reel 5909: frames 410-417) (Box 4)
  - Traveling Exhibition, 1963-1970, (5 folders; Reel 5909: frames 418-480) (Box 4)
  - Oversized Floor Plan of Contemporary Arts Building, World's Fair, New York, 1939-1940, (Reel 5909: 263) (Box 9 (sol))
  - Oversized Poster for Bryant Park Exhibition, 1966-1967, (Reel 5909: 977-978) (Box 9 (sol))
  - Oversized Blueprint Floor Plan of Outdoor Exhibition, 1948, (Reel 5909: 482-483) (Box OV 10)
  - Two Oversized Posters for Bryant Park Exhibition, 1968-1969, (Reel 5909: 1026-1029) (Box OV 10)
- Scrapbooks, 1938-1952, Series 5:; (Boxes 7-9; 0.7 linear feet)
  This series consists of scrapbooks containing clippings and miscellaneous printed material concerning the activities and exhibitions of the Sculptors Guild. Miscellaneous clippings, 1942-1960, notes, a price list and a booklet have been removed from the collection. Twenty-nine pages from Scrapbook 1 and Scrapbook 2 were not microfilmed.
  - Scrapbook 1, 1938, (Reel D266: 60-179) (Box 7 (sol))
  - Scrapbook 2, 1939-1941, (Reel D266: 180-208) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Scrapbook 3 for the 1941 Outdoor Show, 1941, (Reel D266: 209-237) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Scrapbook 4 for the 1942 Outdoor Show, 1942, (Reel D266: 238-263) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Scrapbook for the 1948 Outdoor Show, 1948, (Reel D266A: 458-479) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Scrapbook for the 1948 Outdoor Show, Oversized Clipping, 1948, (Reel D266A: 458-479) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Scrapbook 5, 1951-1952, (Reel D266: 264-304) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Scrapbook, 1939-1940, (Reel 5909: 1038-1065) (Box 9 (sol))
- Printed Material, circa 1938-1974, Series 6:; (Boxes 5-6, OV 10; 0.7 linear feet)
  Printed material includes clippings, press releases, calendars of events, prospectuses for art exhibitions, brochures, and exhibition announcements and catalogs for other exhibitions (not Sculptors Guild). Announcements and catalogs for Sculptors Guild exhibitions can be found in Series 4: Exhibition Files.
  - Brochures, circa 1940-1968, (2 folders; Reel 5910: 546-584) (Box 5 (hol))
  - Calendars of Events, circa 1940-1951, (Reel 5910: 504-514) (Box 5 (hol))
  - Clippings, circa 1938-1974, (41 folders; Reel 5909: 1067-1274; Reel 5910: 13-86; Reel D266A: 19-115) (Box 5 (hol))
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, circa 1938-1941, (Reel 5910) (Box 6 (hol))
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, circa 1939-circa 1958, (Reel 5910: 585-593) (Box 6 (hol))
  - Press Releases, 1940-circa 1969, (4 folders; Reel 5910: 429-503) (Box 6 (hol))
  - Prospectuses, 1939-1972, (see also OV 10; Reel 5910: 515-545) (Box 6 (hol))
  - Oversized Prospectus for the Carol Lane Traffic Safety Award, 1952, (Reel 5910: 535-536) (Box OV 10)
- Photographs, circa 1938, circa 1960s, Series 7:; (Box 6; 1 folder)
  This series consists of one folder of photographs of Guild officers and other individuals. Pictured are: Sarah Churchill, Evan Frankel, and Oronzio Maldarelli; Jessie Earnshaw, William Lescaze and William Pahlman; August Hecksher, Mrs. Raikes, and William Talbot; and Lloyd Goodrich and August Heckscher.
  Additional photographs can be found in 2.2.2: Exhibition Committee Files, Series 3: Artist Files and Series 4: Exhibition Files.
  - Officers and Other Individuals circa 1938, circa 1960s (Box 6 (hol))